A new age has come.
Avengers: Age of Ultron is a action, adventure, science
fiction film directed by Joss Whedon.
When Tony Stark tries to jumpstart a dormant peacekeeping program, things go awry and Earth’s
Mightiest Heroes are put to the ultimate test as the fate of the planet hangs in the balance.
As the villainous Ultron emerges, it is up to The Avengers to stop him from enacting his terrible plans, and
soon uneasy alliances and unexpected action pave the way for an epic and unique global adventure.
Tony Stark / Iron Man, played by Robert Downey Jr..
Thor, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Bruce Banner / Hulk, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Steve Rogers / Captain America, played by Chris Evans.
Natasha Romanoff / Black Widow, played by Scarlett Johansson.
Clint Barton / Hawkeye, played by Jeremy Renner.
Avengers: Age of Ultron (Original Motion Picture Soundtrack) is the film score for the
Marvel Studios film, Avengers: Age of Ultron by Brian Tyler and Danny Elfman.
Hollywood Records released the album digitally on April 28,
2015, and in physical formats on May 19, 2015.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence (a.i.),
saving the world, superhero, based on comic, sequel.
The tone is thought_provoking.